Guide to the Congregational Church Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Congregational Churches in the United States: Regional, State, and Local Records, Series V
  - Vermont
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Charter and By-Laws: Vermont Congregational Conference, 1945 (Box 65, Folder 265)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Champlain Association of Congregational Churches, 1941 (Box 65, Folder 265)
      - Chittenden County Conference of Churches, articles and confession of faith and covenant, 1851 (Box 49, Folder 200)
      - Rutland County Conference of Churches, historical papers, 1900 (Box 49, Folder 200)
    - Individual Churches (see: Record Group 48)
  - Washington (see also regional organizations)
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of General Congregational Association, 1907 (Box 50, Folder 201)
      - Minutes of General Congregational Conference, 1908-1915 (Box 50, Folder 202)
      - Handbook, Congregational Conference, 1920, 1926-1928 (Box 50, Folder 203)
  - Wisconsin
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Record of Congregational Convention, 1902, 1904, 1906 (Box 51, Folder 204)
      - Reports, constitution of Congregational Conference, 1934-1945, 1947-1950 (Box 51, Folder 205)
      - Jubilee Memorial of Congregational Convention, 1840-1890 (Box 51, Folder 206)
      - Minutes of the Annual Meeting of the Presbyterian and Congregational Convention, 1858 (Box 51, Folder 206)
    - Intrastate organizations and meetings
      - Madison Association of Congregation Christian Churches and Ministers (Box 65, Folder 267)
    - Individual Churches
      - Beloit: First Congregational Church, 1896 (Box 52, Folder 207)
      - Beloit: First Congregational Church, 1890 (Box 67, Folder 5)
      - Green Bay: Union Congregational Church, 1911 (Box 52, Folder 207)
      - Milwaukee: Mayflower Congregational Church, 1974 (Box 52, Folder 207)
      - Wauwatosa: Congregational Church, 1882 (Box 52, Folder 207)
  - Wyoming
    - Statewide organizations and meetings
      - Minutes of Congregational Association and Women's Missionary Union, 1905, 1907 (Box 52, Folder 208)
      - Minutes of Congregational Conference and Women's Missionary Union, 1908, 1909, 1911, 1914, 1916, 1917, 1931 (Box 52, Folder 209)
  - Regional Organizations and Meetings
    - Congregational Asso
    - Middle Atlantic Conference of Congregational Churches
      - MACCC - Minutes and Reports, 1920-1926 (Box 52, Folder 210)
      - MACCC - By-laws, 1947 (Box 65, Folder 270)
    - South-Western Conference of Congregational Churches and Ministers/South-Western Congregational Association
      - SWCCCMSWCA: General, 1870, 1871, 1877, 1879-1882 (Box 52, Folder 211)
    - New England Congregational Congress
      - NECC: Report, 1908 (Box 52, Folder 212)
    - Pacific Coast Congregational Alliance
      - Booklet: "Christian Education by Congregationalists on the Pacific Coast", 1893 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Synod of New York and Philadelphia, and the Association of Connecticut: Convention of Delegates (held annually)
      - SNYPAC:CD - General, 1843 (Box 52, Folder 213)
    - Susquehanna Association (New York and Pennsylvania)
      - SA (NYP): General, 1878 (Box 52, Folder 214)
    - Washington Association (District of Columbia, Virginia, Maryland and Delaware)
      - WA: General, 1943 (Box 64, Folder 238)
    - Washington Congregational Conference (Washington, Northern Idaho, Alaska)
      - WCC: General, 1948 (Box 65, Folder 266)
    - Southern Convention of Congregational Christian Churches, Inc. (Virginia, North Carolina)
      - SCCC, Inc.: General, 1948, n.d. (Box 65, Folder 268)
    - Southeast Convention Congregational Christian Churches (Alabama, Georgia, Kentucky, Tennessee)
      - SCCCC: General, ca. 1948 (Box 65, Folder 269)
    - Southern California and the Southwest Conference (California, Arizona, New Mexico, Nevada, Texas)
      - SCSC: Congregational Conference, 1945-1956 (Box 65, Folder 271)
      - SCSC: United Church of Christ, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 272)
    - Triennial Convention of Ministers and Delegates of the Congregational Churches in the Northwest
      - TCMDCCN: General, 1858 (Box 65, Folder 276)